<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<recipe>
<name>Pizza Dough</name>
<img>pizza.jpg</img>
<totaltime>40</totaltime>
<ingredients>Makes enough for 1 12'' pizza, medium thickness, or 1 10'' very thin pizzas

2 1/2 teaspoons instant yeast 
1 tablespoon sugar
284 grams (1 1/4 cups) water
382 grams (13 1/2 ounces) bread flour (about 3 cups)
2 tablespoons olive oil, plus additional for drizzling
1 teaspoon salt
28 grams (1 ounce) grated parmesan cheese)</ingredients>
<type>3</type>
<videoname>null</videoname>
<step>
<speed>10</speed>
<temp>0</temp>
<time>10</time>
<describe>Add all ingredients.

Repeat the blending 4 times by pressing "cook again", total, until dough is cohesive.</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>0</speed>
<temp>0</temp>
<time>0</time>
<describe>Add about 1 tablespoon of olive oil to a plastic bag, then transfer the dough to the bag. Seal the bag and refrigerate for a few hours or up to 3 days.</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>0</speed>
<temp>0</temp>
<time>0</time>
<describe>When you're ready to use the dough, heat the oven to 450 degrees with a pizza stone in the oven.</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>0</speed>
<temp>0</temp>
<time>0</time>
<describe>Remove the dough from the refrigerator. Flour your work surface and turn out the dough. Form the dough into a ball (or divide in half and form into 2 balls, if you wish to make 2 smaller pizzas)</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>0</speed>
<temp>0</temp>
<time>0</time>
<describe>Roll the dough into a flat disk that will fit your pizza paddle (to transfer the pizza) and your pizza stone. Add sauce and toppings as desired.</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>0</speed>
<temp>0</temp>
<time>0</time>
<describe>Transfer the pizza to the stone in the oven (alternatively, you can bake the pizza on a pizza pan, or form it on parchment paper and transfer the pizza to the oven on the parchment).</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>0</speed>
<temp>0</temp>
<time>0</time>
<describe>Bake at 450 degrees until the crust is browned on the bottom and edges and the cheese is melted and bubbling and the toppings are hot. A small, thin pizza will take 8-10 minutes; a larger pizza will take 15 minutes or more.</describe>
</step>
</recipe>