<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<recipe>
<name>Meatballs and Tomato Sauce and Penne</name>
<img>pasta and meatballs.JPG</img>
<totaltime>4210</totaltime>
<ingredients>Meatballs:
1 pound ground beef
2 scallions, thinly sliced
1 egg
1/2 teaspoon salt
1 tablespoon dry parsley
Ground pepper, to taste
1/4 cup bread crumbs

Tomato sauce:
1/2 onion (100 grams)
1/2 green bell pepper
1 tablespoon olive oil
1/2 teaspoon salt
1 tablespoon dry oregano
1 teaspoon dry basil
1/2 teaspoon ground fennel
Pinch of red pepper flakes
1/4 cup red wine
14.5 ounce can (411 grams) petite diced tomatoes
29 ounce can (822 grams) tomato sauce
Grated cheese (optional)

Pasta:
2 quarts water
Salt
1lb penne</ingredients>
<type>3</type>
<videoname>null</videoname>
<step>
<speed>0</speed>
<temp>0</temp>
<time>0</time>
<describe>Make meatballs:
Combine all of the meatball ingredients in a medium bowl and mix with your hands until combined. Form the meat into 12 even balls. Fry the meatballs in a sauté pan until browned on all sides.</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>10</speed>
<temp>0</temp>
<time>10</time>
<describe>Make Tomato Sauce:
Peel the onion and cut in half. Remove the stem, core, and seeds from the green pepper. Place the onion, green bell pepper, and oil in the mixing bowl.</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>3</speed>
<temp>110</temp>
<time>600</time>
<describe>Scrape down bowl. Add the salt, oregano, basil, fennel, and red pepper flakes to the bowl.</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>3</speed>
<temp>90</temp>
<time>3600</time>
<describe>Scrape down bowl. Add the red wine, diced tomatoes, and tomato sauce.
Place the basket in the mixing bowl. Add the meatballs to the basket.
</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>1</speed>
<temp>130</temp>
<time>1080</time>
<describe>Remove meatballs and set aside covered to keep warm. Clean the mixing bowl and basket. Return the mixing bowl and basket to the machine. Fill the mixing bowl up with 2 quarts of water. </describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>1</speed>
<temp>130</temp>
<time>60</time>
<describe>Add pasta and cook according to the time on the packaging.</describe>
</step>
<step>
<speed>0</speed>
<temp>0</temp>
<time>0</time>
<describe>When pasta is done, carefully remove the inner container .Serve the meatballs and sauce with pasta. Garnish with grated cheese, if desired.

The meatballs can also be served as meatball sandwiches with sauce, and the remaining sauce can be served with pasta.
</describe>
</step>
</recipe>